xmlwindataweb.net 2008-08-20

# Privacy Policy | firstlook.com

Updated: June19, 2008

PRIVACY POLICY

Your privacy is important to Firstlook, Inc., a Connexus company, so we have created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our web sites and when we serve advertisements on our network of websites (collectively, the “Firstlook Network”), why we collect it and how it is used.

The terms “you,” “your,” and “yours” refer to the web surfer and/or consumer utilizing our Network. The terms "Firstlook,” “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Firstlook, Inc. and its partners. 

Please read this privacy policy carefully since by visiting this site and sharing information with Firstlook you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our website Terms and Conditions. To the extent there is a conflict between the terms of this Privacy Policy and a written agreement to which Firstlook is party, the terms of such agreement shall prevail with respect to the parties to that agreement.

For more information about Firstlook and other Connexus companies please visit [www.connexuscorp.com](http://www.connexuscorp.com/ "www.connexuscorp.com").

I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
The Firstlook Network contains more than 1,000 websites to which we deliver advertisements and which you, the web surfer, may occasionally visit. During your visit to the Firstlook Network, Firstlook and/or our third party vendors may collect certain information, as follows.

Personally Identifiable Information

“Personally Identifiable Information” or ”PII” means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including first and last name, physical address, email address, or telephone number. 

Firstlook uses technology, including technology from its third party advertising vendors, which includes cookies, “web beacons” and/or “action tags.” A “cookie” is a small text file stored by your browser on your computer when you visit our Network. A “web beacon” or “action tag” is a small image (usually 1x1 pixel) embedded in a web page or email. We use cookies, web beacons and action tags to collect non-personally identifiable data to provide better and more relevant services and messages to that user. Cookies, web beacons and action tags permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information.

To access certain websites operated by Firstlook in the Firstlook Network, we may ask you to register and provide certain PII. Firstlook is committed to making sure that you have clear notice and choice before sharing any PII and that you have opted-in to our use of such information. Web surfers who have provided PII may elect to have their data deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the requested service, by following the procedures set forth below in the "Access" section below.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Firstlook also automatically receives and records anonymous information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website which is part of the Firstlook Network. We use log files to collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser, and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us. This information may be stored on our systems for about one year.

As a rule, non-personally identifiable information is anonymous and is not used to identify a specific person by Firstlook.

Web surfers may elect not to provide non-personally
